Here y'go, Onii-chan!
(小町)はい お兄ちゃん これ
≪(小町)小町オススメ
お土産リスト！
It's my recommended souvenirs list! Dun da-da-dun!
ドンドン パフパフ～
Number three...
第３位！ うん
(比企谷)生八ツ橋
Raw yatsuhashi...
Ganso, Honke, or Honten will be accepted!
元祖でも本家でも
本店でもいいで～す
Number two...
第２位！ うんうん
定番！ あぶらとり紙
The classic: oil blotting paper.
Remember to get enough for Mom, too!
こちら ママンの分もよろしくです
では 待望の第１位は？
And the much-anticipated number one is...
Komachi's recommended souvenirs list!
#1 After the commercial break
#2 Secret ancient Japanese facial paper
#3 Fresh yatsuhashi
#1 After the commercial break
What is number one?
第１位は何だよ
The number one souvenir would be...
一番のお土産は
お兄ちゃんの素敵な思い出だよ
your wonderful memories, Onii-chan!
Sly, but cute.
<あざとかわいい…>
≪(戸塚)八幡 八幡ってば
Hachiman, come on...
うん…
なッ…
Hachiman...
(材木座)八幡…
ウノって言ってな～い イエーイ
You didn't say "Uno." Yay...
お前 別のクラスだろ
イエー
You're not even in my class.
Yay...
♬～
Ninja
Shuriken
Scariest Haunted House in History
m 570.93 315.99 b 570.93 316.99 570.93 317.99 570.93 318.99 569.6 318.43 568.94 317.43 568.93 315.99 569.6 315.99 570.26 315.99 570.93 315.99
(優美子)隼人 怖い～
Hayato, I'm scared!
(戸部)やばい やばい やばい
やばい やばい やべえ！
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
≪(海老名)グフ ウフフ…
(川崎)ヒッ！➡
I just heard a weird voice!
今 なんか変な声が…
(結衣)私 こういうの苦手
I can't handle stuff like this...
お化け屋敷の幽霊なんて
怖くないだろ
Ghosts in haunted houses aren't scary.
What's really scary are people.
怖いのは人間だ
出た ひねくれ
There's that cynical attitude again...
でも ちょっと頼りになるかも
I find it kind of reliable, though.
What I mean is, haunted houses
つまり 人が脅かすタイプの
お化け屋敷が一番怖い
where people scare you are the most terrifying.
Never mind! I can't rely on that!
ダメだった
まったく頼りにならない！
あッ 戸塚
全然平気そうだな
Hey, Totsuka, you seem totally cool with this.
(戸塚)うん 僕
こういうの好きだから
Yeah, I like this sort of thing.
ぶるぁ～！
うわ～ッ！
あッ
川崎さん？
Kawasaki-san?
川崎さ～ん
Kawasaki-san!
痛～ッ
Ow...
あッ ごめん
痛くなかった？
S-Sorry! Did that hurt?
いや 超痛かったけど
Yeah, it hurt like hell.
ほら
えッ？
N-No, I...
いや…
I mean, you know...
まあ 何だ…
ありがとう
Thanks.
Well, let's go.
じゃあ 行こっか
ギャーッ！
Scariest Haunted House in History
m 570.93 315.99 b 570.93 316.99 570.93 317.99 570.93 318.99 569.6 318.43 568.94 317.43 568.93 315.99 569.6 315.99 570.26 315.99 570.93 315.99
終わった…
It's over...
That was pretty scary.
結構 怖かった
That was really fun, huh?
すっごく楽しかったね
Yeah...
(葉山)結構 遊び倒した感じだな
そろそろ行くか
Well, I think we've played enough.
Ready to get going?
Okay, I'll get Ebina.
したら 海老名 呼んでくんね
Wooden swords are so expensive!
木刀たっけーッ
海老名 行くよ
Ebina, let's go.
お化け屋敷の効果が出てるのかな
I wonder if the haunted house had any effect...
どうだかな
Hard to say.
There we go.
よっこらせっと
(雪乃)あら 奇遇ね
Well, what a coincidence.
You're here, too?
お前も こっち来てたの？
ええ
Yes.
虎の子渡しの庭という
別名があるそうよ
This garden is also called "Tiger Cubs Crossing the Water," you know.
どの辺りが虎なのかと思って
Which parts do you think are the tigers?
Hmm... Did that interest her because tigers are cats?
<ほう やっぱ虎もネコ科だから
気になったんですかね>
<こいつ
猫大好きフリスキーだもんな>
She loves cats like they love Friskies.
あッ ゆきのん
Oh, Yukinon!
場所を変えましょうか
Let's go somewhere else.
How's that job coming?
依頼の調子は どう？
う～ん 結構難しいね
ねッ？
It's pretty tough... Right?
あんま やりすぎて海老名さんに
嫌がられてもな それに…
We don't want to push too hard and make Ebina-san like him less.
Plus...
There's one person who can't catch a clue.
<一人 解せない行動を
取っているやつがいる>
それに 何？
Plus what?
Oh... Nothing.
いや 何でもない
任せきりになってしまって
ごめんなさいね
I'm sorry to leave this all to you.
No problem! Don't worry about it!
全然 気にしないで
It's no substitute for actual help,
代わりといってはなんだけど 一応
私のほうでも考えてみたの
but I have been thinking about this.
何をだ？
About what?
Famous places in Kyoto that girls might like.
女性に好まれそうな京都の名所
彼らの参考になればと思って
I thought it might help them.
わあ ゆきのん さすが
You're always on the ball, Yukinon!
では 私は戻るわ
All right, I'm heading back now.
Okay! See you tomorrow!
うん じゃあ また明日
Yes, tomorrow.
ええ また明日
ヒキオじゃん
Hey, it's Hikio.
≪(優美子)あんさ～
あんたら一体 何してるわけ？
Listen, what exactly are you guys up to?
あんま 海老名に
ちょっかい出すのやめてくれる？
Could you stop trying to mess with Ebina?
Are you listening?
聞いてんの？
聞いてる
I'm listening. And we're not messing with her.
それに 別に
ちょっかい出してるわけじゃない
Yes, you are. It's pretty obvious.
出してるでしょ
見てれば分かるし
そういうの迷惑なんだけど
迷惑か
That's a nuisance, you know.
Is it?
There's someone who's asking us to do it, though.
でも そうしてほしいってやつも
いるからな
Besides, it's not like it hurts you or anything.
それに お前は直接的な被害を
受けてるわけでもない
Huh?
はあ？ これから被害受けんの
It's about to hurt me.
あんたさ 結衣と
つきあってるんなら
If you're with Yui, you should know about Ebina.
海老名のことだって
分かるっしょ
I-I-I'm not "with" her.
別に全然つきあってねえし
何 勘違いしてんの？ キモッ
What did you think I meant? Gross.
結衣がヒキオと
つきあうわけないじゃん➡
As if Yui would go out with you.
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
That's not what I meant.
そういうのじゃなくて 何？➡
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
I meant, if you talk with Yui a lot, you should know.
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
結衣と話してたりしたら
分かるでしょってこと キモッ
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Guys love
long-sleeved
cardigans
Some girly yet
casual items to go with
Girlfriend jeans
Gross.
You didn't have to add that on a second time...
<もう一回 付け足さなくてもいい
じゃないですか>
Ebina appeals to guys as long as she's not talking,
海老名 黙ってれば男受けいいから
紹介してくれってやつ 結構いんの
so a lot of them ask to be introduced to her.
But once they're introduced, she turns them down really gently.
でも 紹介しようとすると
超やんわり拒否ってさ
I thought she was being shy,
てれてんだと思って
あーしも結構しつこく勧めたわけ
so I tried pretty hard to push things along.
したら あいつ 笑いながら➡
But she laughed and said,
あッ じゃあ もういいやって
"Oh, never mind, then."
あーしのこと
超他人みたいな感じで言ったの
As if I were a total stranger.
海老名は 自分のこと
あんまり話さないし
Ebina doesn't talk about herself much, and I don't ask,
あーしも別に聞かない
けど そういうの嫌いなんだと思う
but I don't think she likes that kind of thing.
That's not exactly right.
<それは少し違う>
<何かを守るために
いくつも犠牲にするくらいなら>
If you had to sacrifice many things to protect one,
you're more likely to give up and throw it away.
<諦めて捨ててしまうのだろう>
Including the relationships you have in your hand now.
<今 手にしている関係さえも>
あーしさ 今 結構楽しいんだ
I'm having a lot of fun right now.
So I'd appreciate it if you didn't butt in.
だから よけいなこと
しないでくれる？
それなら心配ない
うん？
You don't have to worry, then.
Hayama said he'd do something about it.
葉山が
どうにかするっつってたからな
What the heck?
なんそれ？
まあ 隼人が言うならいいけど
Well, if Hayato said that, then it's fine.
Wow! Awesome!
わあ～ すご～い
う～ん 絶景だ 町が見える
ちょっと休憩だな
Break time...
What a great view! I can see the city!
I agree.
そうね
Oh, it's Tobecchi!
あッ とべっちだ
やっはろ～
Yahello!
いやはや また会ったね
Wow, we meet again, huh?
Hikitani-kun, you haven't forgotten what we discussed, have you?
ヒキタニ君
相談 忘れてないよね？
Huh? Oh...
うん？ ああ…
どう どう？ メンズ達の仲は
睦まじい？
Well? How's it going among the men?
Happy and harmonious?
仲は いいんじゃないか
夜とかトランプしてるし
They're getting along fine, I guess.
They play cards together at night.
But I can't see that! That's not tasty at all!
それじゃ 私が見れないし
おいしくないし
What I really want is for the guys to be
もっとさ 私のいるところで
男子達が固まってるの見るのが
all close together where I can see them!
一番いいんだけどな
Well, we're going to Arashiyama, too, so maybe then...
まあ 俺達も嵐山行くし
そのとき…
よろしくね
I'm counting on you.
Randen Arashiyama Station
夕食 入らなくなるわよ
You're going to spoil your dinner.
Huh?
えッ？
じゃあ ヒッキーにあげる
いらねっつの
Then you can have it, Hikki.
No, thanks.
<なんで ちょっとずつ半端に
口をつけちゃうの この子は>
Why does she just take one little bite from each thing?
If we were splitting them half-and-half, I'd eat it.
<せめて半分こ とかなら
食べたんですけど>
What do I do with these, Yukinon?
これ どうしよう
ゆきのん
ハァ… 少しだけね
All right, just a little.
あなたも手伝いなさい
You help, too.
Well, I can eat some, I guess...
まあ 食べられるけど
Oh, then...
じゃあ…
Here.
はい
うん
<何だか 餌付けされている気分だ
悪くない>
I sort of feel like an animal being fed.
Not bad. Food I didn't have to work for tastes awesome.
<働かずに食べるご飯って
超うまい>
うわ～ すごいね ここ
This place is amazing!
Yes... And look at the ground.
ええ それに足元
灯籠か
Lanterns, huh?
This is it! I bet this is the place!
ここだ ここがいいよ たぶん！
For what?
何が？
To be c-confessed to.
こ… 告られる なら
<なぜ 受動態？>
Why the passive voice?
It does look like a good location.
ロケーションとしては
いいんじゃないかしら
Doesn't it?
だよね
戸部が勝負すんなら
If Tobe's going to go for it,
ここか
I guess this is the place.
Oh, man! I'm getting nervous! Oh, man!
緊張してきた やべえ～
(大和)大丈夫だ
It'll be fine.
Tobe's getting a girlfriend, huh?
(大岡)戸部も彼女持ちか 俺と
遊んだりしなくなるんだろうな
You probably won't want to hang out with me anymore...
That's so not true!
そんなことねえから…
Anyway, oh, man!
ああ～ てか やべえわ
大丈夫だ
It'll be fine.
Even I'm getting nervous.
なんか こっちまで緊張するね
Hey, Tobe...
(葉山)なあ 戸部
何 何？ 隼人君
What, Hayato-kun? I'm kinda freaking out right now.
今 俺 結構テンパってんだけど
Uh, nothing.
いや 何でもない
何だよ～
What is it?
I was just going to say "good luck,"
頑張れって言おうと思ったけど
顔見たら 言う気が失せた
but once I saw your face, I didn't feel like it anymore.
ひどくね？
でも なんか緊張解けてきたわ
Harsh, man!
I feel a little less nervous, though...
やけに非協力的だな
You're being awfully uncooperative.
そうかな
Am I?
そうだろ
You are.
むしろ
邪魔されてた気がするけどな
In fact, it felt as if you were trying to interfere.
≪(葉山)そういうつもりは
なかったんだけどな
That wasn't my intent.
俺は 今が気に入ってるんだよ
I just like things as they are now.
戸部も 姫菜も
みんなでいる時間も
I like Tobe and Hina, and the time we all spend together.
結構好きなんだ だから…
So—
If this is enough to ruin that,
was it really that strong to begin with?
それで壊れるくらいなら 元々
その程度のもんなんじゃねえの？
You might be right, but...
そうかもしれない けど…
失ったものは戻らない
What's lost won't ever come back.
そんな上っ面の関係で
楽しくやろうってほうがおかしい
It's more ridiculous that you're
trying to enjoy superficial relationships like that.
Is it?
そうかな 俺は
これが上っ面だなんて思ってない
I don't think of it as superficial.
今の俺にとっては
この環境がすべてだよ
Right now, the environment I'm in is everything to me.
No, it is superficial.
いや 上っ面だろ
じゃ 戸部はどうなる
What about Tobe, then?
何度か
諦めるようには言ったんだ➡
I told him over and over to give up.
今の姫菜が
心を開くとは思えないから➡
I can't see Hina opening her heart to him right now.
それでも 先のことは分からない➡
But still, I don't know what's in the future.
So I didn't want Tobe to rush to a conclusion...
だから 戸部には
結論を急いでほしくなかったんだ
Pretty selfish thing to say.
勝手な言い分だな
それは お前の都合でしかない
なら…
That's just for your own convenience.
Then...
君は どうなんだ？
What about you?
What would you do?
君なら どうする？
俺の話なんて
どうでもいいだろ
What I'd do doesn't matter.
Just thinking "If it were me..." is a waste of time.
<きっと 俺なら
なんて考えるだけ無駄だ>
<俺と葉山は違う>
Hayama isn't like me.
<戸部だって もちろん違う>
Neither is Tobe, of course.
How I think or feel means nothing whatsoever,
<俺の話なんて
本当に どうでもいい話で>
and it's pointless to talk about.
<本当に どうしようもない話だ>
つまり お前は
何も変えたくないってことだな
So in other words, you don't want anything to change.
ああ そうだ
Yeah, that's right.
You're the last person I wanted to turn to.
君にだけは
頼りたくなかったのにな
<お互いさまだよ バカヤロウ>
The feeling is mutual, idiot.
<葉山が
守ろうとしているものなんて>
I don't understand what Hayama's trying to protect.
<俺には分からない
分からないままでいい>
And I don't need to.
<だから できることがある>
That's why there's something I can do.
戸部
Tobe.
Uh, Hikitani-kun...
ああ ヒキタニ君
やべえわ
This is nuts! I'm totally freaking out right now!
今の俺 かなりキテるわ
Listen, what'll you do if she rejects you?
なあ お前 ふられたら
どうするんだ？
Isn't it kinda harsh to say that before I tell her?
言う前からそれって ひどくない？
いいから早く答えろ
Just hurry up and answer me.
海老名さん 来ちゃうだろ
そりゃ諦めらんないっしょ
Ebina-san will be here soon.
I still wouldn't give up!
I'm not a very serious person, you know?
俺さ こういう適当な人間じゃん？
But I'm pretty serious about this!
けど 今回
結構マジっつーかさ
そうか なら
最後の最後まで頑張れよ
I see. Then do the best you can, until the very end.
Yeah!
おう やっぱヒキタニ君
いいやつじゃん
You're a good guy after all, Hikitani-kun!
違えよ バカ
I am not, idiot!
ヒッキー いいとこあるじゃん
So you can be nice, Hikki.
What brought that on?
どういう風の吹き回し？
そうじゃないんだよ マジで
It's nothing like that, seriously.
このままだと戸部は ふられる
At the rate it's going, Tobe will be rejected.
そうかもしれないわね
You may be right.
そう だね
Yeah...
For what it's worth, there's a way to wrap this all up neatly.
一応 丸く収める方法はある
どんな方法？
What sort of way?
Well, I'll leave this to you.
まあ あなたに任せるわ
うん
Yep!
あッ…
あの…
So, um...
うん
Yeah.
<まず 間違いなく
戸部はふられる>
For starters, there's no doubt she'll turn him down.
<戸部自身には
多少の覚悟はあるだろう>
Tobe must be somewhat prepared for that.
But the others...
<だが 他は？>
Tobe isn't the only one who values their relationships.
<彼らの関係を大事に思っている
のは戸部だけではない>
<だから 彼女は
あんな依頼を出してきたのだ>
That's why she came to us with that request.
And that's why he suffered so much.
<だから 彼は
ああも苦悩していたのだ>
<なくしたくない
その手に つかんでおきたい>
He doesn't want to lose it.
He wants to keep it in his hand.
There's one thing all three of them want.
<三者の願いは 一つだ>
Listen, I...
俺さ その…➡
Um... Um...
その…
To not see Tobe get rejected,
<戸部をふられないようにし かつ
彼らのｸﾞﾙｰﾌﾟの関係性を保ち>
and to keep their group close while staying good friends with Ebina-san.
<海老名さんとも
仲いいままにしておく>
Then there's really only one way!
<なら やっぱ
方法は一つしかねえじゃねえか>
L-Listen...
あ… あのさ
俺…➡
I...
俺…
俺さ…
I...
ずっと前から好きでした
I've liked you for a long time.
Please go out with me.
俺と つきあってください
(竹林が揺れる音)
≪(海老名)ごめんなさい➡
I'm sorry.
I don't intend to go out with anyone right now.
今は誰とも つきあう気がないの
誰に告白されても
つきあう気はないよ
No matter who tells me they like me,
I won't go out with them.
あッ…
話 終わりなら
私 もう行くね
If that's all you wanted, I'm going now.
あッ…
(走り去る足音)
だとよ
You heard her.
ヒキタニ君 それはないでしょ～
Hikitani-kun, that wasn't cool, man.
いや ふられる前に分かって
よかったけどよ
I mean, I'm glad I found out before she could reject me,
but that was not cool. So not cool.
ないわ～
いや ないわ～
まだ時期じゃないってことだろ
That just means this isn't the time, right?
今は この関係を楽しんでおくのも
いいんじゃないか？
What's wrong with enjoying the friendship you have now?
Yeah, I guess...
まあ そうな
いうても 今はって言ってたし
She did say "right now."
Hikitani-kun.
ヒキタニ君 悪いけど
Sorry, but I won't let you win!
俺 負けねえから
Come on, now.
すまない
ああ？
Sorry.
Huh?
I knew that was the only way you knew how to do things.
君は そういうやり方しか
知らないんだと分かっていたのに
Sorry.
すまない
謝るんじゃねえよ
I don't want your apology.
I hate the way you do things.
あなたのやり方 嫌いだわ
ゆきのん…
Yukinon...
うまく説明できなくて
もどかしいのだけれど
It frustrates me that I can't explain why, but...
I really hate that you handle things that way.
あなたの そのやり方
とても嫌い
ゆきのん…
Yukinon...
先に戻るわ
I'm going back.
あッ… 私達も戻ろっか
Sh-Should we head back, too?
そうだな
I guess.
いや～ あの作戦はダメだったね
Well, that plan failed, huh?
I was definitely surprised,
確かに驚いたし 姫菜も
タイミング逃しちゃったけどさ
and Hina didn't get to say what she wanted to either, but...
だな
Yeah.
But... I was pretty shocked.
けど… うん
結構ビックリだった
一瞬 本気かと思っちゃったもん
For a second, I thought you were serious.
As if.
そんなわけないだろ
だよね アハハ…
I guess, huh?
But...
でも…
でもさ
But, listen...
こういうの もう なしね
Don't do stuff like that again, okay?
あれが一番 効率がよかった
それだけだ
It was the most effective way. That's all.
効率とか そういうことじゃないよ
I'm not talking about effectiveness.
解決を望まないやつもいる
There are some people who don't want a solution.
現状維持がいいってやつもいて
みんなに都合よくはできないだろ
Some want things to stay the way they are.
There's no way to make things convenient for everyone.
And as I'm saying all this, it hits me.
<言っているうちに自覚してしまう
これは詭弁だ>
So the only option is to find a compromise.
I'm just rationalizing.
This is the kind of deception I hated more than anything in the world.
<俺が この世で最も嫌った欺瞞だ>
とべっちも ふられてないし
Tobecchi didn't get rejected,
and the guys seem to be getting along well.
男子も なんか仲よさげで
Hina didn't have to worry, either.
姫菜も気にしなくて済んで
Now things will be back to normal from tomorrow on.
これで また明日から
いつもどおり
変わらないで済むのかもしれない
Maybe nothing will have to change.
けど… けどさ
But... But, you know...
あッ…
人の気持ち もっと考えてよ！
You should give more thought to how other people feel!
なんで いろんなことが分かるのに
それが分からないの？
How is it you understand so much,
but you don't understand that?
ああいうの やだ
I can't stand that.
(ため息)
≪(海老名)はろはろ～
Hello, hello!
お待たせしちゃった？
いや
Did I keep you waiting?
Nope.
お礼 言っておこうと思って
別に言わなくていい
I wanted to thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
相談されたことについちゃ
解決してない
I didn't resolve the thing you consulted me about.
表向きはね でも…
Not on the surface, but...
理解してたでしょ？
You understood, didn't you?
<男子同士を仲よく というのは>
You wanted me to get the guys closer
<自分から男子を遠ざけてほしい>
so you could keep them at a distance from yourself,
<ひいては 戸部の告白を未然に
防いでほしいということだ>
and stop Tobe from confessing to you before it happened.
<これは 葉山にも
相談していたのだろう>
You probably talked to Hayama about this, too.
<だから 葉山は悩み>
That's why Hayama
became stressed and had no choice but to act the way he did.
<ああいう中途半端な態度を
取るしかなかった>
Thanks for everything you did. It really helped.
今回は ありがとう
助かっちゃった
Tobe's an idiot and a loser, but he's a nice guy, I think.
戸部は ダメで
ゴミカスみたいな人間だが
いいやつだと思うけどな
無理 無理
Still, I couldn't.
だって 今の私が
誰かとつきあったって
Even if I hooked up with someone right now, it wouldn't work out.
うまくいきっこないもん
That's not...
そんなことは…
あるよ
It is true.
I'm really messed up.
私 腐ってるから
なら しょうがないな
I guess there's no helping that, then.
Nope, there's not.
≪(海老名)そう しょうがない
フフフ…
Maybe I'd be able to go out with you, Hikitani-kun.
私 ヒキタニ君となら
うまく つきあえるかもね
Don't even joke about that.
冗談でも やめてくれ
If you say stuff carelessly, someone might fall in love with you.
あんまり適当なこと言われると
うっかり ほれそうになる
そうやって どうでもいい人には
素直になるとこは嫌いじゃないよ
I sort of like the way you can be so honest with people
who don't matter to you.
What a coincidence.
奇遇だな 俺も自分の
そういうところが嫌いじゃない
I sort of like that about myself, too.
Hey, I can appreciate a person who can say things
私だって こういう心にもないこと
スパッと言えちゃうとこ
he doesn't mean so easily.
嫌いじゃないよ
私ね 今の自分とか
自分の周りとかも好きなんだよ
You know, I like myself and everything around me right now.
こういうの久しぶりだから
なくすのは惜しいなって➡
I haven't felt like that in ages, so I don't want to lose it.
今いる場所が
一緒にいてくれる人が好き
I like where I am, and I like the people here with me.
だから…
That's why...
私は 自分が嫌い
I hate myself.
<大事だから 失いたくないから>
Because it's precious, because you don't want to lose it,
<隠して 装って>
you hide it away and put up a front.
<だから 誰もが嘘をつく>
That's why everyone lies.
<けれど>
But...
<一番の大嘘つきは>
The biggest liar of all
His and Her Confessions
Won't Reach Anyone.
<俺だった>
was me.
#03 Silently, Yukinoshita Yukino Makes Her Decision.
♬～
Sure is quiet without Onii-chan around.
Right, Ka-kun?
I hope Onii-chan's getting along okay.
It's so boring without Onii-chan around.
Ka-kun, let's play!
Good kitty, good kitty! You're so cute!
Your fur's so smooth! Good kitty, good kitty!
Hey, Ka-kun! Where are you going?
I hope he comes home soon.
≪(小町)ああ～
お兄ちゃんいないと静かだね➡
ねえ カー君 おりゃりゃ…
(カマクラの鳴き声)
≪(小町)お兄ちゃん うまく
やってるかね？ ねえ カー君
(カマクラの鳴き声)
お兄ちゃんいないと暇だな
カー君 遊ぼう➡
よ～し よしよし
かわいいでちゅね➡
毛並みﾂﾔﾂﾔでちゅね
よ～し よし➡
わあ～ カー君 どこ行くの？➡
ああ… 早く帰ってこないかな